<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>weekly-picks on Robin Thrift</title>
    <link>https://robinthrift.com/tags/weekly-picks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in weekly-picks on Robin Thrift</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/RobinThrift&#34;&gt;Robin Thrift&lt;/a&gt; 2023</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robinthrift.com/tags/weekly-picks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Picks No. 6</title>
      <link>https://robinthrift.com/posts/weekly-picks-no-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinthrift.com/posts/weekly-picks-no-6/</guid>
      <description>These are programming and non-programming things I found interesting this past week (18.04.16 - 24.04.16):
Rolling Random Romans by Joël Quenneville: Excellent little tutorial on Elm. Launching Mission Control Day (part 1) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Picks No. 5</title>
      <link>https://robinthrift.com/posts/weekly-picks-no-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinthrift.com/posts/weekly-picks-no-5/</guid>
      <description>These are programming and non-programming things I found interesting this past week (11.04.16 - 17.04.16):
BSD for Linux Users: Although a bit dated, it&amp;rsquo;s still an excellent essay by Matt Fuller on the differences both on the technical and philosophical aspects of BSDs and Linux. Passive event listeners: a new DOM API proposal that should help with performance when using scroll handlers (especially on mobile). Table for two: Our favorite two-player board games onby Aaron Zimmerman on Ars </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Picks No. 4</title>
      <link>https://robinthrift.com/posts/weekly-picks-no-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinthrift.com/posts/weekly-picks-no-4/</guid>
      <description>These are programming and non-programming things I found interesting this past week (28.03.16 - 03.04.16):
This should totally be a thing: https://twitter.com/davechenell/status/710549108692541440 String Types in Rust by Andrew Brinker S3Git is &amp;ldquo;git for Cloud Storage&amp;rdquo;, a clever little tool, that allows one to easily sync files with &amp;ldquo;distributed, decentralized and versioned repositories&amp;rdquo;. It uses the BLAKE2 Tree Hashing Algorithm for both deduplicated and hydrated storage Wekan: I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Wekan for a while now, and absolutely love it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Picks No. 3</title>
      <link>https://robinthrift.com/posts/weekly-picks-no-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinthrift.com/posts/weekly-picks-no-3/</guid>
      <description>These are programming and non-programming things I found interesting this past week (25.01.16 - 31.01.16) and why:
github.com/zeithq/micro Very intersting micro services library with a beautifully minimalistic API. An excellent example for good APIs. Typescript 1.8 Beta I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of Typescript and the 1.8 release will make it even better, allowing for easier JS and TS interop. I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to using it. Alduin Colourscheme I&amp;rsquo;ve been using base16-ocean (light and dark) up until now, but I instantly fell in love with this colourscheme, and am now using it both for my terminal as well as vim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Picks No. 2</title>
      <link>https://robinthrift.com/posts/weekly-picks-no-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinthrift.com/posts/weekly-picks-no-2/</guid>
      <description>These are programming and non-programming things I found interesting this past week (14.12.15 - 20.12.15) and why:
Intel NUC I bought this little barebones PC along with a 120GB SSD and 8GB RAM to be used as a simple home server. So far, I have nothing but good things to say about this little machine. Installing Ubuntu Server 14.04 LTS went without a hitch and Docker runs like a charm. It can easly handle anything I throw at it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Picks No. 1</title>
      <link>https://robinthrift.com/posts/weekly-picks-no-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinthrift.com/posts/weekly-picks-no-1/</guid>
      <description>These are programming and non-programming things I found interesting this past week (10.11.14 - 23.11.14) and why:
Golang Examples Learning a new language, and especially one with so many interesting features, is difficult without good examples. Gyver A clever little tool that helps you organize your thoughts and ideas or just gives you inspiration. Little Secret by Nikki Yanofsky Note, I found them this week, it does not mean they are new this week.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
